[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121114pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "RB", "WP", "VBP", "VBN", "RP", "CC", "VBN", "DT", "RB", "NN", "JJR", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "CC", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "CC", "DT", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJR", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "NN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 24, "question": "He seems to be through friends, colleagues, whoever it may be clearing himself really in doing anything wrong, is that right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NNS", ",", "NNS", ",", "RB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBG", "PRP", "RB", "IN", "NN", "NN", "IN", ",", "VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 25, "answer": "Yes, we have a couple of sources now who have come out and given a little bit more information about him and the nature of that relationship between him and a you said, it seems like it's more of a friendship with the families than anything else.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Fran Townsend"], "TIME": ["this evening"]}, "docId": "121114pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "NN", ",", "VBD", "VBN", "DT", "DT", "RB", "NN", "RB", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 35, "question": "But what we're hearing again from sources is that she, too, in relation to confidential material found in her computer, she may be in the clear as well?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "RB", "IN", "NNS", "VBZ", "IN", "PRP", ",", "RB", ",", "IN", "NN", "TO", "JJ", "NN", "VBD", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 36, "answer": "Yes, Fran Townsend, our national security contributor, had reported this a little bit earlier this evening.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121114pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 58, "question": "How convinced are you that you're right in your suspicions that there is genuine foul play here?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBN", "VBP", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "WDT", "EX", "VBZ", "NN", "NN", "NN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 59, "answer": "Well, I would say this.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121114pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 77, "question": "Do you accept that part of the defense?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 78, "answer": "Piers, I think it begs the question.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121114pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "TO", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "WDT", "PRP", "VBD", "JJR", "CC", "EX", "VBP", "JJR", "NNS", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "CD", "IN", "CD", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 85, "question": "Are we talking about a major cover-up by the White House designed to protect the narrative of we are defeating al Qaeda or was it simply just, you know, pretty poor performance by all the people out the line in dealing with this attack?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "JJ", "NNP", "CC", "VBD", "PRP", "RB", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 86, "answer": "Well, it's why we need to get to the bottom of all of these questions that I identified earlier and there are more questions, because it's either one of two things.", "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["White House"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["General Mattis"], "LOCATION": ["Middle East"], "PERSON": ["Petraeus", "Allen", "Stavridis"]}, "docId": "121114pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "POS", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "IN", "EX", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "VBG", "VBN", "NN", "DT", "NN", "TO", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "RB", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "WP", "VBZ", "VBG", "NN", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "CC", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "WP", "VBZ", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 101, "question": "You know, this is a serious time for world affairs and that is why the focus really needs to be right back on to this pretty quickly, doesn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "DT", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", "NNS", "CC", "IN", "VBZ", "WRB", "DT", "NN", "RB", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "RB", "RB", "IN", "TO", "DT", "NN", "RB", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 102, "answer": "Well, I think that's right and I can assure you that while there may be some attention being played inside the beltway to this issue with General Petraeus and perhaps General Allen, Admiral Stavridis is well sighted on what's happening inside the European area and General Mattis is certainly focused on what's happening in the Middle East.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Egypt"]}, "docId": "121114pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "JJR", "VBN", "IN", "WP", "POS", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 111, "question": "What do you think?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 112, "answer": "Well, I'm more concerned about what's going to happen in Egypt.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121114pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "RP", "."], "qSentId": 122, "question": "Under these circumstances could he have possibly ridden this out, do you think?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "NNS", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "RB", "VBN", "DT", "RP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 123, "answer": "Well, he himself felt that he couldn't ride it out.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121114pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "CC", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 133, "question": "And isn't it time collectively as a society maybe we looked at this or do you think that the discipline it has to be the case?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "VB", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "CC", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 134, "answer": "Well, it's about ethical and moral leadership.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121114pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 155, "question": "Tell me why I shouldn't be incredulous?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "WRB", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 156, "answer": "You should not be so excited over that issue.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121114pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "PRP", "VBP", "WP", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 174, "question": "Why wouldn't they have just gone straight to the White House the moment they knew the investigation was concluded?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "JJ", "TO", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 175, "answer": "I'm not sure I understand what conspiracy you want me thinking about.", "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["White House"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121114pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", "IN", "NN", "PRP", "MD", "."], "qSentId": 180, "question": "Unless of course the classified documents that now appeared to be on a computer turned out to be highly sensitive and that would take it to a different realm, wouldn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "IN", "NN", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "WDT", "RB", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "RP", "TO", "VB", "RB", "JJ", "CC", "IN", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "TO", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "MD", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 181, "answer": "But of course it would.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121114pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 208, "question": "Now that intelligence may have been flawed but she was still the go-to person for the White House, wasn't she?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "DT", "NN", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "VBN", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "VBD", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 209, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["White House"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121114pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", ":", "PRP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 236, "question": "Should he have resigned?", "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 237, "answer": "I personally -- it's his personal decision, I don't question his decision.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121114pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 284, "question": "Could you have ever imagined, when you were out there embedded with these troops, that that would happen?", "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "RB", "VBN", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "RP", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", ",", "IN", "DT", "MD", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 285, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121114pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 306, "question": "It is just a total distraction, isn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 307, "answer": "It is.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Petraeus"]}, "docId": "121114pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", ":", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 323, "question": "What do you say to that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 324, "answer": "Well, I don't think the idea -- the problem is that General Petraeus had an affair.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["Sunday"], "PERSON": ["George Stephanopoulos"]}, "docId": "121114pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "IN", "DT", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "NNP", "IN", "NN", "IN", "``", "DT", "NNP", ".", "''"], "qSentId": 337, "question": "What do you think?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 338, "answer": "First of all, I was substituting for George Stephanopoulos that Sunday as host of \"This Week.\"", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121114pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "JJ", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 355, "question": "Did she act in good faith, do you think?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "JJ", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 356, "answer": "I can't get inside her brain.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121114pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "NN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 380, "question": "Why even set a deadline?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "RB", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 381, "answer": "Well, because if you don't set a deadline in this town, nothing happens.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121114pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "WDT", "VBZ", "VBN", "VBN", "VBZ", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 403, "question": "What do you make of it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 404, "answer": "I think the biggest mistake that has been made is starting the investigation to begin with.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Jill Kelley"]}, "docId": "121114pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "IN", "DT", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 411, "question": "Do we know that was the way she was with Petraeus?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 412, "answer": "No, we just think that Jill Kelley is generally a bit like that with all the military guys.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Petraeus"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121114pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "VBG", "CD", "NN", "CC", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "``", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", ".", "''"], "qSentId": 425, "question": "If you were on the \"Today Show,\" how would you play this?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "``", "NN", "NNP", ",", "''", "WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 426, "answer": "I wouldn't be judging one way or the other if I was on \"The Today Show.\"", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121114pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 428, "question": "Wouldn't your viewers instinctively have felt that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "RB", "VB", "NNS", "RB", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 429, "answer": "I don't -- I think they would have been split.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121114pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 439, "question": "What?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "."], "aSentId": 440, "answer": "Except for me.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121114pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "VBG", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 446, "question": "What do you mean?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 447, "answer": "OHEN: Well, I mean, I think this was an egregious over reaching of authority.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121114pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", ",", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 457, "question": "It does seem, when you put it like that, doesn't it, just innately trivial and damaging?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "VB", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "DT", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", ",", "RB", "RB", "JJ", "CC", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 458, "answer": "It is, absolutely.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121114pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", ",", "RB", ",", "IN", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBZ", "CC", "WP", "NN", "NN", "VBZ", "IN", "PRP", "CC", "WP", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 467, "question": "It is a different game, isn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 468, "answer": "And it's just tragic, too, because of who he is and what respect everybody has for him and what he has sacrificed for this country.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121114pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBZ", "RB", "VB", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "."], "qSentId": 508, "question": "Really?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 509, "answer": "And does not let anybody near her.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121114pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 510, "question": "Really?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 511, "answer": "Yeah.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121114pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP$", "NNS", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 514, "question": "You did?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 515, "answer": "Well, our kids did.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121114pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 531, "question": "Why invest all of this emotional time in something that won't last?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "DT", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", "WDT", "MD", "RB", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 532, "answer": "Because they're part of your family.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121114pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 534, "question": "Did Rocky Balboa not love you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 535, "answer": "Rocky didn't last very long.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121114pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 554, "question": "And anyone that does love animals, or even feels the way that you do and I do, a bit ambivalent about it, it's a classic family pet story, isn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "NN", "IN", "VBZ", "VB", "NNS", ",", "CC", "RB", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 555, "answer": "It is.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121114pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 577, "question": "First time \"The Today Show\" has had a woman really at the top, right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NN", "``", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "''", "VBZ", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "RB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 578, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121114pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "NN", "IN", "``", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", ".", "''"], "qSentId": 582, "question": "Could you be lured back?", "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "VBN", "RP", "."], "aSentId": 583, "answer": "I'm doing stuff for \"The Today Show.\"", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121114pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 585, "question": "What does that mean?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 586, "answer": "Whatever you want it to mean.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121114pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "RB", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 594, "question": "Why do you give me that look?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 595, "answer": "It must be quietly satisfying.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121114pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "RB", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 605, "question": "Which one was I?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WDT", "CD", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 606, "answer": "He is the pretty one.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121114pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 613, "question": "Is it hard to get that kind of chemistry, do you think?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 614, "answer": "I think chemistry is very difficult.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121114pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 629, "question": "Do you watch any of them?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 630, "answer": "I watch them all.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}]